Support Admin Watch on
kissasia.cam or kisskh.org
♪In ancient times, a meteor fell♪
♪Scorching Nanba Weald into land bare♪
♪From Turquoise Land beneath the sun♪
♪The evil Earth Fiends were born♪
♪Marching in South Mountain's domain♪
♪Sworn warriors raged for glory's gain♪
♪Renamed guardians hold Yanguan true♪
♪Peace in all lands, a priceless boon♪
♪Seven hounds, two whips, one blade♪
♪In rout and flight,
Earth Fiends escape♪
♪Golden Gate seals fast♪
♪South Mountain Hunters
on the righteous path♪
=Love on the Turquoise Land=
(This story is a work of fiction)
=Episode 9=
I'm helping you with a huge favor.
And you brush me off with this?
The Hunters' magic weapon?
Only I have this.
Ordinary weapons won't cause
substantial damage on Earth Fiends.
But this works wonders.
Like using garlic against
vampires?
That's one way to put it,
but the mechanism differs.
Its design is for easy concealment.
But remember.
This isn't a weapon,
but something helps you escape
at critical moments.
It can't launch an attack.
And, Jiang Baichuan recognizes it.
Well...
Wait a second.
You gave me such a crucial tool.
May I ask
what is Jiang Baichuan to you?
He's the leader of the Hunters.
He raised me.
I see. Like a mentor and father to you.
No time to waste.
Go fulfill your promise now.
Your plan to completely quit the Hunters
has delayed, right?
Free to join or quit
and act as you please.
It's never easy.
Even revered monks practicing lifelong
may never achieve so.
Enough philosophical talk.
Let's get some breakfast.
You stay. I'll get some.
(Breakfast)
Two, please.
Thanks.
Got it.
Hey.
What will you have?
What's available?
Everything. Look yourself.
Alright, two of each then.
Right away.
Wait a moment.
Breakfast.
How long were you out there?
Not long. It's still warm.
Thanks, but I'm not hungry.
Been up all night?
Impressive. No food, no rest.
So you Hunters fight
against Earth Fiends
through sheer willpower?
Even without food or rest,
Jiang still got captured.
Just tell me what you want me to do.
Roadsound Group's influence in Xicang
is tremendous.
Even with all evidence in hand,
Lin Xirou could still
use her connections
and excuses to stall for time.
Especially she has Jiang
as their hostage now.
Reckless moves would alert her
and endanger Jiang.
When I first met Lin Xirou as a child,
she looked exactly like this.
Many years have passed,
she looks still the same.
That's right.
Earth Fiends have long lifespans.
So time is what she lacks the least.
She acts with meticulous care,
caution and endless patience.
Roadsound has weathered
multiple business crises.
No matter the opponent,
she could stay composed
and counterattack.
Of course.
To fight us short-lived ones,
time favors her.
She waits for us to panic
and blunder.
Hence, we can't act recklessly.
While caution matters,
we can't stay passive.
For example?
Make her hurt.
Put cartons in cold chain.
The rest goes on next truck.
Drive faster. No delays.
Got it, Zheng.
By the way, Zheng,
can I take two days off
after this delivery?
Why now?
My mom's hospitalized, needs surgery.
I'll go check on her.
Then skip this delivery
and go now.
Family matters.
No need, Zheng.
Not that urgent.
My mother still needs more observation.
She might not need surgery.
(Purifies air, absorbs formaldehyde)
Are you sure?
Don't force it.
Not at all.
Not at all, Zheng.
I'll go now, Zheng.
(Message)
Get off me!
(Bangcheng Business Travel)
You forgot something.
Keep forgetting things.
Miss me, okay?
I'm leaving.
Bye.
(History of the World)
Our trip to Xicang this time
for camping or a picnic?
Eat it or not. No question.
If a woman treated me this well,
I wouldn't leave her.
Sis.
Lin Ling is not a kid anymore.
No need for you
to escort her every time.
Ms. Lin asked you
where you went this morning.
Ms. Lin asked me?
Ms. Lin intended to escort her herself,
but saw you rushing out
without going to the office,
so sent me to check.
Alright, I'll call her later.
Ms. Lin said you can just tell me,
and I'll relay it to her.
I-I just went for breakfast.
Breakfast?
I scrolled through videos last night.
Guess what I saw?
The fried breadstick store
Ms. Lin often bought us to. Remember?
The one behind our school?
Exactly! Seeing it made me so hungry.
I even stayed up all night
from craving.
So I went straight there
this morning
and bought a bunch.
But,
I barely ate a few bites.
Look, they're still on the table.
When it comes to food,
Lin Ling's pastries are the best,
tasty and healthy.
Who knows if the breakfast store
uses the recycled oil, right?
Take care.
When people grow up,
they can't taste the flavors
in childhood anymore.
Met your helper again?
Any progress?
Only bad news.
Ms. Lin captured their man.
To keep her helping us,
I must help her this time.
I have bad news too.
(Car Rental Reimbursement Itinerary,
Roadsound Group, Xicang City)
What's this?
(Benben Budget Hotel)
From the files we saw earlier,
those unregistered humanoid Earth Fiends
are all coming to Xicang.
They're planning something big.
Send me the photos.
Then delete them all.
Including our chat history.
Is it that serious?
Didn't you see how solemn Sis was?
You're under Ms. Lin's watch,
in grave peril.
So you must not be discovered.
Understand?
These people are coming over here.
Is it for the person you mentioned
that Ms. Lin captured?
(Available today? Usual spot.)
(Okay.)
Sent.
(Car Rental Reimbursement Itinerary)
What is this?
A group of humanoid Earth Fiends
are coming to Xicang.
Others are flying in.
Xiong Hei handles the pickup,
leaving us no chance.
But two are driving from nearby
separately by car.
They'll stop at the hotel in Shihe.
Sent you the details.
Coming.
The usual.
Thank you.
What's your plan?
Let's start by targeting these two.
Eat up.
At times like this,
you have to have enough food.
What you sent is useful.
I need to figure out how to use it.
Miss, you've brought
your boyfriend here so many times.
Why don't you try our signature dessert?
This one's on the house.
Wishing you a sweet relationship!
Hello.
I have a plan.
It might rescue Jiang.
Go on.
A group of humanoid Earth Fiends
are coming to Xicang.
Capture them
and trade with Lin Xirou.
Where did you get this news?
Don't you trust me?
Even if we capture them,
are you sure she'll make the trade?
Once they reach Roadsound,
we'll lose our chance.
What's the plan?
I'll tail them first.
You stake out their destination.
I'll send you the location.
Don't take your own car to tail them.
I know. I rented one.
Tell everyone
to get moving.
(List, License Plates)
(Mount Anping Tunnel, 1320m long)
Has this happened before?
Wait, look.
They're rushing us to Xicang this time.
And there are so many of us.
No idea.
Pull over at the service area.
I'll take a leak.
We can't be late.
No music.
No chatting.
Not even leaks?
The Hound Clan of the Hunters
can track us by scent.
Thanks to Ms. Lin,
we've taken human form
without any scent.
But if I can't hold it and wet my pants,
the Hounds...
m-must smell me from afar.
Look at you.
You never talk to me,
instead, you take my joke
pretty seriously.
Let's go.
Move now. You said we can't be late.
That blue car's been tailing us.
At the service area now.
Still some distance away.
But they've spotted me.
I'll reinforce you.
No. Ambush them at the hotel.
What if they attack you?
Even better.
If we fight at the hotel,
it'll be more complicated.
If they act rashly,
I'll take them down here.
Luo, don't be reckless.
Alright, don't worry.
I drive slowly.
You'll have time to cook
after I exit the highway.
See you tonight.
Let's go.
Is it necessary?
Cut the crap.
(Small Potato
Where are you now?)
(Need me to come over?)
She's really following us.
Stay alert.
Just a woman.
Stop her and interrogate her.
She might have backup.
Let's go to a quiet spot first.
- Let's go.
- Okay.
Take your stuff.
(Nie Jiuluo
Need me to come over?)
(Yan Tuo)
Sorry, the subscriber you dialed...
Where are they?
What time is it?
7 PM.
Sorry,
the subscriber you dialed
is unavailable.
Please try again later.
Sorry,
the subscriber you dialed
is unavailable.
Let's backtrack along the highway.
(No Service)
Sorry,
the subscriber you dialed
is unavailable.
What? You won't let me
pick trash during the day,
and now won't even
let me sleep peacefully at night?
What are you...
Han Guan.
Han Guan!
Who are you?
Who sent you here?
Han Guan!
Stop shouting.
He can't hear you anymore.
You know how to kill us.
You're
Mad Blade.
Nie Jiuluo!
Nie Jiuluo. You okay?
Nie Jiuluo, are you okay?
Nie Jiuluo.
Wake up.
(Xicang, Shiqing)
Nie Jiuluo, wake up!
Don't pass out.
Luo.
Wake up. We're almost there.
Mom.
Where are we going?
I promised you
a boat ride.
Forgot about it already?
I won't go.
Next time,
how about I take you
to my usual canteen?
A canteen worthy of your taste must
serve upscale French cuisine.
Not at all.
I don't find French cuisine upscale.
Escargot can't beat
the braised duck feet.
The cheese can't beat osmanthus cakes.
You'll definitely love the place
I'll take you.
How do you know
what I like?
Let's give it a try.
Alright.
Looking forward to it.
Here.
Give me five.
♪Dig out the truth buried
beneath the earth♪
♪Heaven-sent tides can't
quench this reckless fire♪
♪If we don't retreat,
we'll go through it together♪
♪Heaven-forged fire
lights up the endless night♪
♪Ripping apart the hidden truth
beneath the surface♪
♪Heaven-sent tides can't
drown this stubborn flame♪
♪Farewell to the old times,
and scenes fade away one by one♪
♪The shapeless fire
clings to matter to illuminate♪
♪Yet malice in darkness
defies the flame's pursuit♪
♪A noble name must do righteous deeds♪
♪After sunrise,
even wise words falter in truth♪
♪Heaven-forged fire
scorches flesh and bone♪
♪Dig out the truth buried
beneath the earth♪
♪Heaven-sent tides can't
quench this reckless fire♪
♪If we don't retreat,
we'll go through it together♪
♪Heaven-kindled flames are different♪
♪Truth's madness is hiding
under the surface♪
♪The large waves are rolling
towards the sky♪
♪Farewell to the old times,
and scenes fade away one by one♪